But I do want to be clear, there are no slaves that work for me here.
Okay, so I just kind of want to make sure legal told me to say,
hi, we don't have slaves here.
We do pay people.
We did kind of borrow from that overseer model
because it kind of works for corporate, okay?
And it's kind of the only model we've kind of been following in America.
And so even right down to the way that we kind of like do our spreadsheets
and keep tabs on, you know, different employees and documents
and things like that, that system was developed then.
And we just kind of added some tech to it.
So there are some benefits to, you know, what slavery has,
they've given America the management system that we have.
So I'm glad we got rid of the whole like actual slaves being slaves.
I'm glad we started to pay people.
But, you know, the role of the manager,
it's kind of always been kind of very pivotal
to making sure that the mission is being driven forward.
So when I think of like, what could the proverbial would be?
Well, you know, now there are a lot of, you know, measures put in place.